---= GANDCRAB =--- 

Attention! 
All your files documents, photos, databases and other important files are encrypted and have the extension: .CRAB 
The only method of recovering files is to purchase a private key. It is on our server and only we can recover your files. 
The server with your key is in a closed network TOR. You can get there by the following ways: 
1. Download Tor browser - https://www.torproject.org/ 
2. Install Tor browser 
3. Open Tor Browser 
4. Open link in tor browser: http://gdcbmuveqjsli57x.onion/5dc65409d6fdfbef                        
5. Follow the instructions on this page 
                         
On our page you will see instructions on payment and get the opportunity to decrypt 1 file for free. 

If you can't download TOR and use it, or in your country TOR blocked, read it:
1. Visit https://tox.chat/download.html
2. Download and install qTOX on your PC.
3. Open it, click "New Profile" and create profile.
4. Search our contact - 6C5AD4057E594E090E0C987B3089F74335DA75F04B7403E0575663C26134956917D193B195A5
5. In message please write your ID and wait our answer: 5dc65409d6fdfbef                           

DANGEROUS! 
Do not try to modify files or use your own private key - this will result in the loss of your data forever! 